<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Mortality Day</string>

    <string name="alert_ok">OK</string>
    <string name="alert_save">Save</string>
    <string name="alert_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="alert_delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="alert_thanks">Thanks</string>
    <string name="alert_warning">Warning</string>
    <string name="alert_info">Info</string>

    <string name="info_message">This app is open source (https://github.com/purposebakery/MortalityDayAndroid). Feel free to submit feedback / comments / quotes via the issues tab. \n\nLauncher icon made by Freepik from www.flaticon.com is licensed by CC 3.0 BY</string>

    <string name="alert_share">Share quote</string>

    <string name="first_start_title">Remind me that I must die, so I grow wise…</string>
    <string name="first_start_message">Welcome to our community of aware mortals! \n\nCheers, Oliver.</string>

    <string name="next_day">Next Mortality Day</string>

    <string name="settings_show_quote">Show Quote</string>

    <string name="notification_title">My Mortality Day…</string>
    <string-array name="notification_messages">
        <item>Remind me that I must die, so I grow wise.</item>
        <item>Don\'t regret growing older. Its a privilege denied to many.</item>
        <item>Live simply so that others may simply live.</item>
        <item>Death is something inevitable. When a man has done what he considers to be his duty to his people and his country, he can rest in peace.</item>
        <item>On the contrary, death is the ultimate fairness; rich and poor, young and old, all are equal in death.</item>
        <item>The best way to find yourself is to lose yourself in the service of others.</item>
        <item>Yesterday is history. Tomorrow is a mystery. Today is a gift. That\'s why it\'s called the present.</item>
        <item>Being sad with the right people is better than being happy with the wrong ones.</item>
        <item>You have enemies? Good. That means you\'ve stood up for something, sometime in your life.</item>
        <item>You are only young once, but you can be immature forever.</item>
        <item>Worrying is like a rocking chair: it gives you something to do, but doesn\'t get you anywhere.</item>
        <item>When another person makes you suffer, it is because he suffers deeply within himself, and his suffering is spilling over. He does not need punishment; he needs help.</item>
        <item>Don\'t fear failure. - Not failure, but low aim, is the crime. In great attempts it is glorious even to fail.</item>
        <item>Not all of us can do great things. But we can do small things with great love.</item>
        <item>Be yourself; everyone else is already taken.</item>
        <item>Evil prevails when good men fail to act.</item>
        <item>It is not death that a man should fear, but he should fear never beginning to live.</item>
        <item>Even death is not to be feared by one who has lived wisely.</item>
        <item>If a man has not discovered something that he will die for he isn\'t fit to live.</item>
        <item>All you have to decide is what to do with the time that is given to you.</item>
        <item>Many that live deserve death. Some that die deserve life. Do not be too eager to deal out death in judgement. Even the very wise cannot see all ends.</item>
        <item>Change your life today. Don\'t gamble on the future, act now, without delay.</item>
        <item>Life is like riding a bicycle. To keep your balance, you must keep moving.</item>
        <item>Do not take life too seriously. You will never get out of it alive.</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="notification_authors">
        <item>Bible</item>
        <item>Unknown</item>
        <item>Mahatma Gandhi</item>
        <item>Nelson Mandela</item>
        <item>Unknown</item>
        <item>Mahatma Gandhi</item>
        <item>Unknown</item>
        <item>Philippos</item>
        <item>Winston Churchill</item>
        <item>Hannah Marks</item>
        <item>Van Wilder</item>
        <item>Thich Naht Hanh</item>
        <item>Bruce Lee</item>
        <item>Mother Teresa</item>
        <item>Oscar Wilde</item>
        <item>Edmund Burke</item>
        <item>Marcus Aurelius</item>
        <item>Buddha</item>
        <item>Martin Luther King, Jr.</item>
        <item>Gandalf</item>
        <item>Gandalf</item>
        <item>Simone de Beauvoir</item>
        <item>Albert Einstein</item>
        <item>Elbert Hubbard</item>
    </string-array>


</resources>
